<archimate:Device
    xmlns:archimate="http://www.archimatetool.com/archimate"
    name="Handheld Two-Way Radios (HTWR)"
    id="id-ab7d5860f8964895b940dbe814b29957"
    documentation="Intended Use: &#xD;&#xA;&#xD;&#xA;•&#x9;Security team patrols and emergency responses &#xD;&#xA;•&#x9;Facilities and maintenance teams &#xD;&#xA;•&#x9;Clinical teams (Emergency Room, Wards, Surgical areas) &#xD;&#xA;•&#x9;Emergency preparedness and disaster management coordination &#xD;&#xA;  &#xD;&#xA;Specifications: &#xD;&#xA;&#xD;&#xA;•&#x9;Frequency Range: &#xD;&#xA;&#x9;o&#x9;UHF (400–470 MHz) preferred for optimal indoor building penetration and clarity across &#x9;multiple floors and buildings. DMR Tier III (Digital Mobile Radio) &#xD;&#xA;•&#x9;Transmit Power: &#xD;&#xA;&#x9;o&#x9;Minimum 4–5 Watts (ensures reliable multi-building and multi-floor coverage within &#x9;campus). &#xD;&#xA;•&#x9;Battery Life: &#xD;&#xA;&#x9;o&#x9;18hrs + solar/wireless charging option for continuous use per full charge, adequate for &#x9;full shifts without interruption &#xD;&#xA;&#x9;o&#x9; rapid charging cradle or spare battery packs for quick swapping. &#xD;&#xA;•&#x9;Durability Rating: &#xD;&#xA;&#x9;o&#x9;IP54–IP67 (water-resistant/splash-proof and dustproof) &#xD;&#xA;&#x9;o&#x9;MIL-STD-810G compliant, drop-resistant from at least 6 ft onto concrete &#xD;&#xA;&#x9;o&#x9;Rugged casing suitable for clinical, security, and facilities environments. &#xD;&#xA;•&#x9;Operating Range: &#xD;&#xA;&#x9;o&#x9;Reliable coverage of at least 250,000–300,000 sq. ft. indoor area (to comfortably exceed &#x9;the hospital’s 163,000 sq. ft. facility and ensure clear signal penetration across multi-story &#x9;buildings). &#xD;&#xA;•&#x9;Connectivity Options: &#xD;&#xA;&#x9;o&#x9;Analog/Digital dual-mode capability (supports smooth transition to digital system for &#x9;improved clarity and privacy) &#xD;&#xA;&#x9;o&#x9; Bluetooth capability (wireless earpieces for hands-free operation). &#xD;&#xA;•&#x9;Size and Weight: &#xD;&#xA;&#x9;o&#x9;Compact and lightweight (&lt;10 ounces) for ease of carrying and prolonged use &#xD;&#xA;&#x9;o&#x9;Approximate dimensions: 5”–6” height, 2”–3” width, 1.5”–2” thickness. &#xD;&#xA;•&#x9;Audio Quality: &#xD;&#xA;&#x9;o&#x9;Clear, distortion-free speaker audio &#xD;&#xA;&#x9;o&#x9;Noise-cancelling microphone for improved clarity in loud clinical or emergency &#x9;environments &#xD;&#xA;&#x9;o&#x9;audio accessories (earpieces, headsets) for discreet and clear communication. &#xD;&#xA;•&#x9;Interface and Control Layout: &#xD;&#xA;&#x9;o&#x9;Simple and intuitive layout &#xD;&#xA;&#x9;o&#x9;Large Push-to-Talk (PTT) button for quick, easy operation (even when wearing gloves) &#xD;&#xA;&#x9;o&#x9;Clearly labeled controls (volume, channel selector knob, emergency alert button) &#xD;&#xA;&#x9;o&#x9;LED indicators for battery status, signal strength, and channel/activity. &#xD;&#xA; &#xD;&#xA;Recommended Accessories: &#xD;&#xA;&#xD;&#xA;•&#x9;Charging Dock and Spare Batteries: &#xD;&#xA;&#x9;o&#x9;Rapid multi-unit charger stations &#xD;&#xA;&#x9;o&#x9;Spare rechargeable battery packs for extended operations. &#xD;&#xA;•&#x9;Carrying Solutions: &#xD;&#xA;&#x9;o&#x9;Rugged belt clips or holsters &#xD;&#xA;&#x9;o&#x9; shoulder harnesses or straps for easy carrying during extended shifts. &#xD;&#xA;•&#x9;Audio Accessories: &#xD;&#xA;&#x9;o&#x9;Wired or Bluetooth wireless earpieces/headsets for hands-free operation and enhanced &#x9;privacy. &#xD;&#xA;•&#x9;Protective Equipment: &#xD;&#xA;&#x9;o&#x9;Durable cases or silicone covers for extra shock and drop protection. &#xD;&#xA;"/>
