<archimate:Node
    xmlns:archimate="http://www.archimatetool.com/archimate"
    name="Decision Support/Data Analytics Server (DSD)"
    id="id-07b81103596345079bb2aa791789da45"
    documentation="Intended Use:&#xD;&#xA;&#xD;&#xA;Specifications:&#xD;&#xA;&#xD;&#xA;•&#x9;Processor Type: &#xD;&#xA;&#x9;o&#x9;Dual Intel Xeon Platinum or AMD EPYC processors (32 cores each) optimized for computational performance. &#xD;&#xA;•&#x9;Memory Capacity: &#xD;&#xA;&#x9;o&#x9;Minimum 512 GB RAM, expandable to 5 TB (supporting large analytical datasets, advanced machine learning, and complex modeling). &#xD;&#xA;•&#x9;GPU Acceleration: &#xD;&#xA;&#x9;o&#x9;2 GPU cards (96gb)  (e.g., NVIDIA Tesla A-series GPUs, such as A100 or equivalent) essential for efficient machine learning and AI workloads.  &#xD;&#xA;•&#x9;Storage Capacity and Configuration: &#xD;&#xA;&#x9;o&#x9;High-performance NVMe local storage (8 TB) for rapid data caching and processing. &#xD;&#xA;&#x9;o&#x9;Additional SAN/NAS storage connectivity for scalable data warehousing. &#xD;&#xA;•&#x9;Network Connectivity: &#xD;&#xA;&#x9;o&#x9;Quad-port 10GbE minimum, preferably 25GbE or higher for rapid data transfer between analytics servers and data warehouses. &#xD;&#xA;•&#x9;Form Factor: &#xD;&#xA;&#x9;o&#x9;Rack-mounted (2U–4U) with adequate internal expansion for GPUs and memory. &#xD;&#xA;•&#x9;Redundancy Features: &#xD;&#xA;&#x9;o&#x9;Redundant power supplies, RAID storage redundancy, redundant network interfaces, hot-swappable components (fans, drives, GPUs where possible). &#xD;&#xA;•&#x9;Power Supply Rating: &#xD;&#xA;&#x9;o&#x9;Dual redundant power supplies (1600W, 80 PLUS Platinum efficiency rating). &#xD;&#xA;•&#x9;Cooling System: &#xD;&#xA;&#x9;o&#x9;Enhanced cooling system with redundant, high-performance hot-swappable fans to manage GPU and CPU heat loads. &#xD;&#xA;•&#x9;Virtualization Support: &#xD;&#xA;&#x9;o&#x9;VMware vSphere, Microsoft Hyper-V, Linux-based hypervisor certified for analytics workloads. &#xD;&#xA;•&#x9;Operating System Compatibility: &#xD;&#xA;&#x9;o&#x9;Windows Server 2022 (with support for analytics platforms) &#xD;&#xA;&#x9;o&#x9;Linux-based servers (RHEL, Ubuntu, CentOS) optimized for data analytics and AI workloads. &#xD;&#xA; &#xD;&#xA;Recommended Accessories and Protection for All Servers: &#xD;&#xA;&#xD;&#xA;•&#x9;Uninterruptible Power Supply (UPS): &#xD;&#xA;&#x9;o&#x9;Rack-mounted UPS system for power outage protection and stable operation. &#xD;&#xA;•&#x9;Server Rack and Cabinet: &#xD;&#xA;&#x9;o&#x9;Secure, lockable 19-inch standard server rack or cabinet with adequate ventilation and cable management. &#xD;&#xA;•&#x9;Remote Management: &#xD;&#xA;&#x9;o&#x9;Integrated management module - Dell iDRAC for remote monitoring and maintenance. &#xD;&#xA;•&#x9;Backup and Disaster Recovery: &#xD;&#xA;&#x9;o&#x9;Cloud or off-site replication &#xD;&#xA;&#x9;o&#x9;Automated scheduled backups &#xD;&#xA;&#x9;o&#x9;Comprehensive disaster recovery planning. &#xD;&#xA;•&#x9;Security Features: &#xD;&#xA;&#x9;o&#x9;TPM 2.0 for encryption &#xD;&#xA;&#x9;o&#x9;Secure Boot capability &#xD;&#xA;&#x9;o&#x9;Regular firmware/security patches updates. &#xD;&#xA;"/>
