<archimate:Device
    xmlns:archimate="http://www.archimatetool.com/archimate"
    name="Clinical-Use Laptops (CL)"
    id="id-0138444d0b0948b68cebe138ebd590da"
    documentation="Intended Use: &#xD;&#xA;&#xD;&#xA;Clinical documentation, EMR access, real-time patient chart updates, bedside patient management, labs, and pharmacy orders. &#xD;&#xA;&#xD;&#xA;Specifications: &#xD;&#xA;&#xD;&#xA;•&#x9;Processor type: Intel Core i7 or AMD Ryzen /7 &#xD;&#xA;•&#x9;Memory capacity: 32 GB RAM &#xD;&#xA;•&#x9;Storage capacity: 1TB SSD  &#xD;&#xA;•&#x9;Screen size and resolution: 13–15 inches, Full HD touchscreen (1920 x 1080). Anti-glare touchscreen – helps reduce eye strain in bright hospital environments. &#xD;&#xA;•&#x9;Battery life: Minimum 10 hours &#xD;&#xA;•&#x9;Operating system: Windows 11 Pro (Healthcare-ready version preferred) &#xD;&#xA;•&#x9;Connectivity options: Wi-Fi 6 (ensure compliance with access points)/6E, Bluetooth 5.1, Ethernet (via adapter and dock), LTE  &#xD;&#xA;•&#x9;Ports and expansion slots: USB-A (x2), USB-C (Thunderbolt or power/video output), HDMI, headphone/microphone jack &#xD;&#xA;•&#x9;Graphics capabilities: Integrated graphics &#xD;&#xA;•&#x9;Build quality and weight: Medical-grade antimicrobial coating, spill-resistant keyboard, rugged construction, under 4 lbs. &#xD;&#xA;•&#x9;Protective Equipment: Ruggedized medical-grade case and screen protector &#xD;&#xA;•&#x9;Included peripherals: Mouse and Keyboard &#xD;&#xA;&#xD;&#xA;•&#x9;Security Features: &#xD;&#xA;&#xD;&#xA;&#x9;o&#x9;RFID or biometric authentication for secure login/logout &#xD;&#xA;&#x9;o&#x9;Privacy screen filter integrated or attached &#xD;&#xA;&#x9;o&#x9;Remote management and location tracking capability &#xD;&#xA;&#x9;o&#x9;TPM 2.0 security module for encryption of patient data &#xD;&#xA;&#x9;o&#x9;Compliant with HIPAA and relevant data security standards. &#xD;&#xA; &#xD;&#xA;•&#x9;Docking Station Support: If used in multiple locations (nurses’ stations, ICU, etc.), ensuring compatibility with a universal dock will enhance workflow. &#xD;&#xA; &#xD;&#xA;•&#x9;Fanless or Quiet Cooling Design – Reduces noise pollution in quiet clinical environments. "/>
