<archimate:Device
    xmlns:archimate="http://www.archimatetool.com/archimate"
    name="High-Security Office Shredder (HSOS)"
    id="id-8d99d964e00f449aa3a8d70f184c52b7"
    documentation="Intended Use: &#xD;&#xA;&#xD;&#xA;•&#x9;Departments: Administrative offices, HR, Finance, Procurement, Medical Records, Pharmacy, Legal, Security. &#xD;&#xA;•&#x9;Purpose: Securely destroying sensitive hospital documents, financial records, patient information, and prescription labels to ensure data protection compliance and prevent unauthorized data recovery. &#xD;&#xA;  &#xD;&#xA;Specifications: &#xD;&#xA;&#xD;&#xA;1. Shredding Capacity: &#xD;&#xA;•&#x9;Minimum 15–30 sheets per pass (standard A4, letter, legal-sized documents). &#xD;&#xA;•&#x9;Supports continuous duty cycle for high-volume shredding. &#xD;&#xA;&#xD;&#xA;2. Security Level: &#xD;&#xA;&#xD;&#xA;•&#x9;P-5 or P-6 Security (for Highly Sensitive Data) – If handling extremely confidential patient records, consider P-6 (≤1mm x 10mm micro-cut) for near unrecoverable shredding. &#xD;&#xA;•&#x9;Cut paper into ≤5mm particles to ensure compliance with healthcare data destruction standards. &#xD;&#xA;&#xD;&#xA;3. Feed Type: &#xD;&#xA;&#xD;&#xA;•&#x9;Auto-feed and manual feed options to allow bulk shredding and on-demand single-page shredding. &#xD;&#xA;&#xD;&#xA;4. Media Compatibility: &#xD;&#xA;&#xD;&#xA;•&#x9;Paper (A4, legal, letter) &#xD;&#xA;•&#x9;Staples &amp; Paper Clips: Can shred documents without removing staples or paper clips. &#xD;&#xA;•&#x9;Credit Cards &amp; ID Badges: slot for shredding expired hospital staff IDs. &#xD;&#xA;•&#x9;CDs/DVDs: Dedicated slot for shredding old data discs. &#xD;&#xA;&#xD;&#xA;5. Bin Capacity: &#xD;&#xA;&#xD;&#xA;•&#x9;Minimum 30–50 liters (8–13 gallons) to reduce frequent emptying. &#xD;&#xA;•&#x9;Pull-out bin design for easy waste disposal. &#xD;&#xA;•&#x9;Bag-compatible for collecting shredded waste securely. &#xD;&#xA;&#xD;&#xA;6. Shredding Speed &amp; Duty Cycle: &#xD;&#xA;&#xD;&#xA;•&#x9;Continuous-duty motor (for high-usage environments). &#xD;&#xA;•&#x9;Auto-reverse &amp; anti-jam technology to prevent paper jams. &#xD;&#xA;•&#x9;Minimum speed: 5–7 feet per minute (fast shredding to reduce downtime). &#xD;&#xA;•&#x9;Higher Speed (7+ feet per minute) – Faster shredding speeds reduce wait times in high-traffic hospital areas (e.g., records, finance). &#xD;&#xA;&#xD;&#xA;7. Noise Level: &#xD;&#xA;&#xD;&#xA;•&#x9;≤55 dB for quiet operation in hospital offices. &#xD;&#xA;&#xD;&#xA;8. Safety &amp; Security Features: &#xD;&#xA;&#xD;&#xA;•&#x9;Auto-stop when bin is full to prevent overloading. &#xD;&#xA;•&#x9;Overheat protection (prevents overheating during long use). &#xD;&#xA;•&#x9;Touch-sensitive safety shutoff to prevent accidental activation. &#xD;&#xA;•&#x9;Lockable casters for easy movement and stability. &#xD;&#xA;•&#x9;Dust Filtration System 9. Power Requirements: &#xD;&#xA;•&#x9;220–240V AC (50Hz) for compatibility with electrical system. &#xD;&#xA;•&#x9;Energy-efficient, auto-sleep mode after inactivity. &#xD;&#xA;"/>
