<archimate:Device
    xmlns:archimate="http://www.archimatetool.com/archimate"
    name="Nursing Documentation Mobile Cart (NDMC)"
    id="id-8a3304acf41f4852bb5b62100db239ff"
    documentation="Intended Use: &#xD;&#xA;&#xD;&#xA;•&#x9;Bedside patient documentation, real-time updates to EMR/EHR, medication administration tracking, patient vitals monitoring, and clinical communication on wards. &#xD;&#xA;&#xD;&#xA;Specifications: &#xD;&#xA;&#xD;&#xA;•&#x9;Screen Size and Resolution: &#xD;&#xA;&#x9;o&#x9;24 FHD Matte Anti-Reflective + Projected Capacitive (P-Cap) touchscreen, providing clarity and usability for detailed clinical documentation. &#xD;&#xA;•&#x9;Touch Interface Responsiveness: &#xD;&#xA;&#x9;o&#x9;High-sensitivity capacitive touchscreen, optimized for clinical use with gloves, stylus, or &#x9;bare hands &#xD;&#xA;&#x9;o&#x9;Multi-touch support for intuitive interactions. &#xD;&#xA;•&#x9;Battery Life: &#xD;&#xA;&#x9;o&#x9;16hr (2x hot-swappable batteries) + USB-C PD charging for continuous runtime per full &#x9;charge, supporting a full nursing shift &#xD;&#xA;&#x9;o&#x9;Hot-swappable battery system for uninterrupted operation. &#xD;&#xA;•&#x9;Connectivity Options: &#xD;&#xA;&#x9;o&#x9;Integrated Wi-Fi 6 (ensure compliance with access points) (802.11ax or higher) for &#x9;reliable wireless connectivity &#xD;&#xA;&#x9;o&#x9;Bluetooth 5.1 or higher for barcode scanners, label printers, and other peripheral &#x9;devices &#xD;&#xA;&#x9;o&#x9;Ethernet connectivity option for wired connections &#xD;&#xA;&#x9;o&#x9;USB-A ports (minimum 3 ports), USB-C, and audio jack for peripheral integration. &#xD;&#xA;•&#x9;Operating System: &#xD;&#xA;&#x9;o&#x9;Windows 11 Pro (Healthcare-ready configuration) with compatibility for hospital &#x9;EMR/EHR and clinical software. &#xD;&#xA;•&#x9;Durability and Build Quality: &#xD;&#xA;&#x9;o&#x9;Medical-grade, antimicrobial surfaces resistant to hospital-grade cleaning solutions &#xD;&#xA;&#x9;o&#x9;Ruggedized construction capable of withstanding frequent use, spills, and accidental &#x9;impacts &#xD;&#xA;&#x9;o&#x9;Spill-resistant keyboard and sealed touchscreen panel. &#xD;&#xA;•&#x9;Weight and Dimensions: &#xD;&#xA;&#x9;o&#x9;Compact, lightweight mobile cart, approximately 18–22 inches width x 18–22 inches &#x9;depth &#xD;&#xA;&#x9;o&#x9;Adjustable height (approx. 36–48 inches) for comfortable ergonomic use &#xD;&#xA;&#x9;o&#x9;Weight optimized for ease of maneuverability (&lt; 40 lbs total). &#xD;&#xA;•&#x9;Security Features: &#xD;&#xA;&#x9;o&#x9;Biometric (fingerprint) or RFID card-based authentication for secure staff login &#xD;&#xA;&#x9;o&#x9;Integrated TPM 2.0 module for secure encryption of patient data &#xD;&#xA;&#x9;o&#x9;Lockable storage compartment for documentation and accessories &#xD;&#xA;&#x9;o&#x9;Remote asset tracking and device management capability &#xD;&#xA;&#x9;o&#x9;Compliant with HIPAA and applicable security standards. &#xD;&#xA;&#x9;o&#x9;Proximity auto-lock (logs out if staff walks away) &#xD;&#xA;•&#x9;Input Methods: &#xD;&#xA;&#x9;o&#x9;Integrated spill-resistant keyboard and multi-touch screen interface &#xD;&#xA;&#x9;o&#x9; clinical stylus input support for precision entry &#xD;&#xA;&#x9;o&#x9;Barcode scanner compatible via USB or Bluetooth for medication and patient ID &#x9;scanning. &#xD;&#xA;•&#x9;Protective Equipment: &#xD;&#xA;&#x9;o&#x9;Bumper guards for impact protection &#xD;&#xA;&#x9;o&#x9;Lockable wheels for stable positioning and safety &#xD;&#xA;&#x9;o&#x9;Antimicrobial screen protector and keyboard cover. &#xD;&#xA;"/>
