<archimate:Device
    xmlns:archimate="http://www.archimatetool.com/archimate"
    name="UPS for Critical Clinical Equipment (Computers on Wheels, Nursing Carts, Clinical "
    id="id-b2d17d84404641b8969fba43feb4d142"
    documentation="1. UPS for Servers (Core Application, Database, Analytics, Virtualization) (UPSS) &#xD;&#xA;&#xD;&#xA;Purpose: &#xD;&#xA;&#xD;&#xA;Protect high-performance, critical servers and data storage systems. &#xD;&#xA;&#xD;&#xA;Specifications: &#xD;&#xA;&#xD;&#xA;•&#x9;Capacity: 3000–6000 VA (3–6 kVA) &#xD;&#xA;•&#x9;Topology: Online (Double Conversion) UPS for highest protection &#xD;&#xA;•&#x9;Runtime: Minimum 15–30 minutes at full load, with expandable external battery options &#xD;&#xA;•&#x9;Input Voltage: 208/220V &#xD;&#xA;•&#x9;Output Voltage: 208/220V (clean, regulated output) &#xD;&#xA;•&#x9;Connectivity: Network management card for remote monitoring and alerts (SNMP compatible) &#xD;&#xA;•&#x9;Features: Automatic Voltage Regulation (AVR), surge protection, hot-swappable battery &#xD;&#xA;•&#x9;Form Factor: Rack-mounted (2U–4U) &#xD;&#xA;  &#xD;&#xA;2. UPS for Networking Infrastructure (Switches, Routers, Wi-Fi APs, Firewalls) (UPSN) &#xD;&#xA;&#xD;&#xA;Purpose: &#xD;&#xA;&#xD;&#xA;Keep critical network infrastructure running without interruption. &#xD;&#xA;&#xD;&#xA;Specifications: &#xD;&#xA;&#xD;&#xA;•&#x9;Capacity: 1500–3000 VA (1.5–3 kVA) &#xD;&#xA;•&#x9;Topology: Line-interactive UPS with AVR (Automatic Voltage Regulation) &#xD;&#xA;•&#x9;Runtime: Minimum 30 minutes &#xD;&#xA;•&#x9;Input Voltage: 120V (50/hz)/220V &#xD;&#xA;•&#x9;Output Voltage: 120V/220V (clean output) &#xD;&#xA;•&#x9;Connectivity: Network management ( SNMP card for monitoring and management) &#xD;&#xA;•&#x9;Features: Surge suppression, noise filtering, hot-swappable batteries &#xD;&#xA;•&#x9;Form Factor: Rack-mounted (1U–2U) &#xD;&#xA;  &#xD;&#xA;3. UPS for Critical Clinical Equipment (Computers on Wheels, Nursing Carts, Clinical Monitors) (UPSC) &#xD;&#xA;&#xD;&#xA;Purpose: &#xD;&#xA;&#xD;&#xA;Ensure critical mobile clinical devices have stable power, avoiding disruptions to patient care.&#xD;&#xA; &#xD;&#xA;Specifications: &#xD;&#xA;&#xD;&#xA;•&#x9;Capacity: 500–1000 VA (0.5–1 kVA) per charging/storage station or nursing station &#xD;&#xA;•&#x9;Topology: Line-interactive or standby &#xD;&#xA;•&#x9;Runtime: Minimum 20–30 minutes &#xD;&#xA;•&#x9;Input Voltage: 120V/50Hz &#xD;&#xA;•&#x9;Output Voltage: 120V (regulated output) &#xD;&#xA;•&#x9;Connectivity:  basic monitoring via USB or Ethernet &#xD;&#xA;•&#x9;Features: Compact, quiet operation, battery failure alerts &#xD;&#xA;•&#x9;Form Factor: Compact desktop or wall-mountable &#xD;&#xA;"/>
