<archimate:Device
    xmlns:archimate="http://www.archimatetool.com/archimate"
    name=" High-Performance Laptops (HPL)"
    id="id-c3c0ce464f6f47a491235c84c8d99f8b"
    documentation="Intended Use: &#xD;&#xA;&#xD;&#xA;Medical imaging, radiology image review (PACS), laboratory data processing, analytics and AI-driven diagnostic applications. &#xD;&#xA;&#xD;&#xA;Specifications: &#xD;&#xA;&#xD;&#xA;•&#x9;Processor type: Intel Core i7/i9 or AMD Ryzen 7/9 &#xD;&#xA;•&#x9;Memory capacity: 64 GB RAM minimum. In addition, more GPU VRAM (12GB+ Recommended) – Some PACS, AI-driven image analysis, and deep learning models benefit from at least 12GB VRAM (e.g., NVIDIA RTX A-series or 40-series). &#xD;&#xA;•&#x9;ECC RAM: ( for Advanced Medical Computing) – If running critical AI workloads, ECC (Error-Correcting Code) RAM improves data integrity. &#xD;&#xA;•&#x9;Storage capacity: 1 TB SSD (NVMe recommended) &#xD;&#xA;•&#x9;Screen size and resolution: 15–17 inches, 4K Ultra HD (3840 x 2160), high brightness, color accuracy. HDR &amp; DICOM Calibration Display  &#xD;&#xA;•&#x9;Battery life: Extended Battery Life ( 10+ Hours for Portability) – If laptops are frequently used away from a dock, consider higher capacity batteries. &#xD;&#xA;•&#x9;Operating system: Windows 11 Pro (Healthcare Ready version preferred) &#xD;&#xA;•&#x9;Connectivity options: Wi-Fi 6 (ensure compliance with access points)E, Bluetooth 5.2, Ethernet (via adapter and dock), LTE/5G &#xD;&#xA;•&#x9;Ports and expansion slots: USB-A (x3), USB-C (Thunderbolt 4), HDMI 2.1, DisplayPort via USB-C, SD Card reader, Ethernet &#xD;&#xA;•&#x9;Graphics capabilities: Dedicated graphics (e.g., NVIDIA RTX series or equivalent). At least 8gb of memory &#xD;&#xA;•&#x9;Build quality and weight: High durability, professional-grade aluminum or magnesium alloy build, under 6 lbs. &#xD;&#xA;•&#x9;Protective Equipment: Reinforced laptop carrying case and keyboard protector &#xD;&#xA;•&#x9;Included peripherals: Mouse and Keyboard &#xD;&#xA;&#xD;&#xA;•&#x9;Security Features: &#xD;&#xA;&#xD;&#xA;&#x9;o&#x9;RFID or biometric authentication for secure login/logout &#xD;&#xA;&#x9;o&#x9;Privacy screen filter integrated or attached &#xD;&#xA;&#x9;o&#x9;Remote management and location tracking capability &#xD;&#xA;&#x9;o&#x9;TPM 2.0 security module for encryption of patient data &#xD;&#xA;&#x9;o&#x9;Compliant with HIPAA and relevant data security standards. &#xD;&#xA;"/>
